

#### **Enrique Whisnant**

Although the cause of death was reported as pneumonia, Enrique, a 25-year-old semi-professional sports person, is convinced that his late girlfriend, Laura Wheeler, was murdered.

He is a British Christian. He started studying sports science at college but never finished the course.

Physically, Enrique is in pretty good shape. He is very short with dark skin, black hair and brown eyes.

He grew up in a working class neighbourhood. Having never really known his parents, he was raised in a series of foster homes.

He is currently single. His most recent romance was with a student called Laura Wheeler, who was the same age as him. Laura died in 2018. The papers reported the cause of death: 'pneumonia'

Enrique's best friend is a semi-professional sports person called Tatiana Graves. They are inseparable. He also hangs around with Kiaran Mathew and Jackson Rowe. They enjoy binge-watching boxed sets together.

#### **Basic Information**

Name:	Enrique Whisnant
	l .

Nickname:	Rude Enrique
Reason for nickname:	Descriptive
Date of birth:	Friday, 14th Oct 1994 (Age 25)
Star sign:	Libra
Nationality:	British
Ethnicity:	Latino/Hispanic
Social class:	Working class
Religion:	Christian
Sexuality:	Unknown
Education:	Some college
Course:	Sports science
Political views:	Right
Relationship status:	Single
Career path:	Athletic

# **Physical characteristics**

Height:	very short
Shape:	average
Build:	average
Hair colour:	black
Eyes:	brown
Glasses/lenses:	none
Distinguishing marks:	none
Other words that might be used:	clipped, little, short, squat, stumpy

### **Personality**

Positive characterist ics:	friendly, careful
Negative characterist ics:	rude, impatient
Words often used:	careful, friendly, impatient, rude
Other words that might be used:	affable, amiable, amicable, aware, blimpish, bounderish, bourgeois, careful, cautious, certain, chummy, close, companionate, comradely, conscientious, conservative, conventional, cordial, couthie, couthy, cozy, crude, deliberate, detailed, eager, early, elaborate, elaborated, favorable, friendly, fusty, genial, heedful, hidebound, ill-bred, ill-mannered, impatient, impatient of, impolite, informal, intimate, intolerant of, lowbred, materialistic, matey, measured, mindful, minute, narrow, neighborly, neighbourly, nonprogressive, painstaking, pally, particular, primitive, provident, raw, restive, rude, scrupulous, short, social, standpat, studious, stupid, sure, thorough, thrifty, traditionalist, troubled, ultraconservative, uncivil, underbred, unforbearing, unhurried, unintelligent, unmannered, unmannerly, unprocessed, unprogressive, unrefined, well-disposed, yokelish
Moral:	sometimes
Stable:	sometimes
Loyal:	sometimes
Generous:	not at all
Extrovert:	sometimes
Compassio nate:	sometimes
IQ:	80
Hobbies:	football, planking, walking, binge-watching boxed sets, theatre, recycling, interviewing suspects, listening to music, worship, watching television, looking for clues
Bad habits:	obsessing over Laura Wheeler's murder
Diet	eats meat

Favourite foods:
------------------

### **Employment**

Golf caddy	Yellowstone Country Club	2010 - 2014	resigne d
Gym assistant	B Fit	2014 - 2017	resigne d
Semi-professional sports person	City Team	2017 - present	

### **Background**

Early years	Enrique grew up in an impoverished neighbourhood. Having never really known his parents, he was raised in a series of foster homes.
Formative years	Enrique got his first job as a golf caddy at age 16 Enrique started college but quit part way through the course.
Most traumatic childhood experience:	His mother leaving when he was two.

## Relationships

#### **Friends**

Louise Robson (Lifespan: 1997 - present)	
Relation	Friend
Occupation	Junior doctor
Age	22
Relationship	They are inseparable

### Rhys Black

(Lifespan: 1992 - present)

Relation	Friend
Occupation	Receptionist
Age	27
Relationship	They have a very firey friendship

#### **Aaron Moran**

(Lifespan: 1996 - present)

Relation	Friend
Occupation	Legal secretary
Age	23
Relationship	They get on well most of the time

#### **Parents**

### Sophie Fowler

(Lifespan: 1971 - present)

Relation	Mother
Occupation	Electrician
Age	48
Relationship	Non-existent.

### Koby Whisnant

(Lifespan: 1948 - present)

Relationship  Siblings	Non-existent.
Age	71
Occupation	Scientist
Relation	Father

### Nabila Fowler

(Lifespan: 1987 - present)

Relation	Half sister (shared mother)
Occupation	Lawyer
Age	32
Relationship	Enrique and Nabila grew up together. Nevertheless, they are not particularly close.

### Mabel Fowler

(Lifespan: 1990 - present)

Relation	Half sister (shared mother)
Occupation	Student
Age	29
Relationship	Enrique is convinced that Mabel was murdered

### **Deborah Whisnant**

(Lifespan: 1984 - present)

Relation	Half sister (shared father)	
Occupation	Senior programmer	
Age	35	
Relationship	Enrique and Deborah spent a lot of time together before their father walked out on Enrique's mum but contact dwindled after that.	

#### **Former Partners**

# Ashley Netta Rice (Lifespan: 1996 - present)

(Liiespan. 1996 - present)		
Relation	Ex-girlfriend (1 year : 2012 - 2013)	
Occupation	Artist	
Reason for breakup	Ashley wanted to be with somebody more vibrant	
Age	23	
Relationship	No longer keep in touch	

Alishia Lynsey Conrad (Lifespan: 1974 - present)		
Relation	Ex-girlfriend (1 year : 2014 - 2015)	
Occupation	Novelist	
Reason for breakup	Alishia was bored	
Age	45	
Relationship	Remained friends	

#### **Political Views**

Abortion:	against
Racial equality:	pro
LGBTQ rights:	very pro
Subsidised healthcare:	undecided
Gun control:	undecided
Nuclear disarmament:	against
Death penalty:	undecided
Tax cuts for the wealthy:	against
Protecting the environment:	against

#### **Timeline**

1994	Age 0	Enrique Whisnant is born
1995	Age 1	Father, Koby Kim Whisnant walks out
1996	Age 2	Mother, Alycia McKinley Arnold walks out
2002	Age 8	Half sister (shared mother), Mabel Evalyn Arnold dies aged 12 (influenza)
2010	Age 16	Starts work at Yellowstone Country Club at golf caddy
2012	Age 18	Gets together with Ashley Netta Rice.
2013	Age 19	Relationship with Ashley Netta Rice ends (Ashley wanted to be with somebody more vibrant).
2014	Age 20	Gets together with Alishia Lynsey Conrad. Resigns from job as golf caddy at Yellowstone Country Club Starts work at B Fit at gym assistant
2015	Age 21	Relationship with Alishia Lynsey Conrad ends (Alishia was bored).
2017	Age 23	Gets together with Laura Wheeler. Resigns from job as gym assistant at B Fit Starts work at City Team at semi-professional sports person
2018	Age 24	Girlfriend, Laura Wheeler dies aged 17 (pneumonia)
2019-1 0-08		Present Day